

+33-7-49-76-09-67 | lindsaykerr1994@gmail.com | 89 Boulevard Baille, Marseille, 13006, France linkedin.com/in/lindsay-kerr-9a8445185/ | github.com/Lindsaykerr1994

PROFILE

Front End Web Developer, specialising in Javascript, primarily working with ReactJs. Confident with Front-end and Back-end tasks, having experience with HTML5, CSS3, Python, PHP and SQL. Constantly evolving my skill sets by undertaking personal and professional projects, exploring programming languages, such as Ruby and Rust, and developing with technologies including, but not limited to, Next.js, Node.js, GraphQL.

Following graduation from Code Institute and a career change, I have been exploring DevOps. With my experiences in a range of industries, I have seen first-hand the need for communication between departments, and I aim to utilise the practices of DevOps, along with my attention to detail and valuable problem solving skills as I pursue a career as a Front End Web Developer creating clean, technology driven and reusable code. I am open to collaboration with fellow developers, hoping to create relationships with peers in the industry.

SKILLS

- + Problem solving & Troubleshooting
- + Attention to detail
- + Communication
- + Time management
- + Team coordination
- + Leadership skills
- + Customer service
- + Interpersonal skills

- + HTML5 & CSS3
- + Javascript, jQuery, Node.js, React JS
- + Python, Django
- + PHP
- + SQL, PostgreSQL, MySQL
- + Microsoft Office
- + VSCode, VSO & Git Pod
- + Git control

PREVIOUS PROJECTS

- + .ONWARDS AND UPWARDS https://www.onwards-and-upwards.com/
 - + Created the back-end database, that allows a user to request an appointment with the adventure company, pay for their session using Stripe capabilities, and enter their information to be stored to create a client/participant model that allows the staff to browse participant information, apply discounts for returning clients. Created using Django in Python.
- + GRIZZLY AUDIO PACKS github.com/Lindsaykerr1994/MS4-Grizzly-Audio
 - + An eCommerce store that specializes in downloadable audio files to be used in music production. The site utilised frameworks such as AllAuth for email verification, Stripe for online payments, and Django for the general app framework
- + CLANKERS SCHEDULING github.com/Lindsaykerr1994/MS3-Appointment-Planner
 - + A Python appointment planning/ scheduling web-based application, using MongoDB to store, create, retrieve, edit and delete data.
- + ATHENA CURRENCY CONVERTER lindsaykerr1994.github.io/Athena-Currency-Converter/
 - + A SPA, simple but effective in design. Utilised API's to display up to date currency rates. Allows the user to convert a numerical amount between two chosen currencies, as well as choose a base currency to compare a table of additional currencies against. Made in ReactJS

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

SALES ASSISTANT - TENDERCARE NURSERIES

June 2019 - February 2020

- + Leader of a sales team, able to take on any responsibility and delegate where necessary.
- + Guided clients through every step of their interaction with the company, from selection and purchasing, to delivery, to installation.
- Regularly orchestrated transactions worth thousands of pounds.
- Go-to employee who assisted in representing the company at trade shows in different cities.

FLOOR MANAGER - HEAP SENG HOUSE

September 2018 - May 2019

- + Handled the day-to-day operations that ensured the success of the business.
- Under my tenure, the restaurant broke the sales record on three separate occasions.
- Constructed schedules, ordered inventory, arranged appointments.
- Served all customer gueries with friendliness and expertise.

STORE MANAGER - BEAN AROUND THE WORLD

February 2017 - August 2018

- Modernized hygiene standards set by provincial food regulations.
- Interviewed potential new employees and trained new recruits.
- Negotiated new contracts with vendors.
- + Launched sales and promotions to encourage new clients.
- Handled cash, wrote employees paychecks and paid monthly bills.

STORE MANAGER - PITA PIT LTD

September 2014 - January 2017

- Initially hired as a line cook, but was promoted to Night Manager, and then to Store Manager.
- Ensured the standards of professionalism, customer service and hygiene.
- + Handled cash every day, confirming the sales report against the daily intake.
- + Communicated with the head office every month to provide a performance report.
- Implemented new promotions as requested by head office.

EDUCATION HISTORY

- **DIPLOMA IN SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT Code Institute, Ireland** Accredited by University of Napier, Edinburgh June 2019 - February 2020
- **ASSOCIATE OF ARTS IN ENGLISH -** Langara College, Vancouver September 2013 - January 2015
- **INTERNATIONAL BACCALAUREATE -** Intl. School Of Penang, Malaysia September 2010 - June 2012

LANGUAGES

- **English** Native
- + French Conversational
- Melayu Conversational
- Japanese Conversational

HOBBIES

- Carpentry
- + Cooking
- Music Production
- Jogging
- Rugby

References are available upon request.

Front End Developer - React / Javascript / AWS / Typescript / Fintech Key Skills: React, React Ecosystem , AWS , Javascript Desirable: React Native, Pvthon. Typescript